Guide to the David L. Call papers, 1977-1995.
Call, David L. papers, 1977-1995
- Personal Enterprise & Small Business Management Program, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Personal Enterprise & Small Business Management Program, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Personal Enterprise & Small Business Management Program, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Personal Enterprise & Small Business Management Program, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Personal Enterprise & Small Business Management Program, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Personnel--University, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Philippines Farming Systems Project, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Philippines Farming Systems Project, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Physiology, Dept. of, 1984-1987 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Physiology, Dept of, 1984-1987 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Planning & Budgeting (M.C. Nesheim, Vice President), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Plant Biology, Section of, 1984-1987 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Plant Biology, Section of, 1984-1987 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Plant Breeding, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Plant Breeding, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Plant Pathology, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Pomology, Dept. of, 1984-1987 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Pomology, Dept. of, 1984-1987 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Ponds, Committee to Evaluate Cornell, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Population & Development Program (International Population Program), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Poultry & Avian Sciences, Dept. of, 1984-1987 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Poultry & Avian Sciences, Dept. of, 1984-1987 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Poultry Research Farm--Operational Plans for, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- Presidential Scholars, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- Pro-Fac Cooperative, Inc., 1985-1987 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- Pro-Fac Cooperative, Inc., 1985-1987 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- Provost (Robert Barker), 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 35)
- Provost (Robert Barker), 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- Provost (Robert Barker), 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 37)
- Provost (Robert Barker), 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 38)
- Provost (Robert Barker), 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 39)
- Provost (Robert Barker), 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 40)
- Provost (Robert Barker), 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 41)
- Public Affairs (Richard Ramin), 1984-1987 (Box 32, Folder 42)
- R (General Correspondence), 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 43)
- Real Estate, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 44)
- Research, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 45)
- Research, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 46)
- Research, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 47)
- Research (J.M. Ballantyne, Vice President), 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Research (B.F. Chabot, Office of the Director), 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Research (B.F. Chabot, Office of the Director), 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Research (B.F. Chabot, Office of the Director), 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Rhodes, Frank, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Rhodes, Frank, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Roby Athletic Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1980-1987 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Rural Safety Council, NYS Dept. of, 1984-1987 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Rural Schools Program, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Rural Sociology / Sociology Merger, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- S (General Correspondence), 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Salaries, 1983-1987 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Science, Technology, & Society, Program on, 1986-1988 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Sea Grant Institute, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Sea Grant Institute, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Sea Grant Governing Board, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Sea Grant Governing Board, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Sea Grant Governing Board, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Sea Grant Governing Board, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Sea Grant Governing Board, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Seafood Technology Laboratory, 1983-1987 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Seafood Technology Laboratory, 1983-1987 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Seafood Technology Laboratory, 1983-1987 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Senators, 1985-1987 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Seneca Foods, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Seneca Foods, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Senior Vice President (James E. Morley, Jr.), 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Senior Vice President (William G. Herbster), 1985-1987 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Shoals Marine Laboratory, 1978-1987 (Box 33, Folder 33)
- Sponsored Programs (T. Rogers), 1987 (Box 33, Folder 34)
- Student Services, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 35)
- Students, Dean of (David Drinkwater), 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 36)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 37)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 38)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 39)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 40)
- SUNY--Chancellor, Office of the, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 41)
- SUNY--Chancellor, Office of the, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 42)
- SUNY--Chancellor, Office of the, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 43)
- SUNY--Chancellor, Office of the, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 44)
- SUNY--Chancellor, Office of the, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 45)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 46)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 47)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 48)
- SUNY--Institutional Research & Planning, Office of, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- SUNY--Institutional Research & Planning, Office of, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- SUNY--Institutional Research & Planning, Office of, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- SUNY--Institutional Research & Planning, Office of, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- SUNY--Provost, Office of the, 1984-1986 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- SUNY--Provost, Office of the, 1984-1986 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- T (General Correspondence), 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Title XII, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Toxicology & ICET (Institute for Comparative & Environmental Toxicology), 1984-1986 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Toxicology & ICET (Institute for Comparative & Environmental Toxicology), 1984-1986 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Toxicology & ICET (Institute for Comparative & Environmental Toxicology), 1984-1986 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- U (General Correspondence), 1987 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Uihlein, Henry (Donor), 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Uihlein, Henry (Donor), 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Undergraduate Education, Cornell Commission on, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Undergraduate Education, Cornell Commission on, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Undergraduate Education, Cornell Commission on, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Undergraduate Education, Cornell Commission on, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Undergraduate Education, College Study Group on, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Undergraduate Education, College Study Group on, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Undergraduate Education, College Study Group on, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- United Way, 1984-1987 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- University Council, 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- University Council, 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- University Counsel, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- University Counsel, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- University Counsel, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- University Relations (John F. Burness, Vice President for), 1986 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- USDA, 1984-1987 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- V (General Correspondence), 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- Vegetable Crops, Dept. of, 1984-1987 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- Vegetable Crops, Dept. o, 1984-1987 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Vegetable Crops--Chairmanship, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 33)
- Veterinary College, 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Vice Provost (J.W. Spencer), 1986 (Box 34, Folder 35)
- Vice Provost (J.W. Spencer), 1986 (Box 34, Folder 36)
- W (General Correspondence), 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 37)
- Warren, Stanley Teaching Endowment Fund, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 38)
- Washington Symposium on Science & Technology, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 39)
- Washington Symposium on Science & Technology, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 40)
- Wing, Kenneth E., Associate Dean, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 41)
- Wing, Kenneth E., Associate Dean, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 42)
- Wing, Kenneth E., Associate Dean, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 43)
- Wing, Kenneth E., Associate Dean, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 44)
- Wolf Foundation, 1984-1987 (Box 34, Folder 45)
- Academic Programs, Office of, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Academic Programs, Office of, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Academic Programs, Office of, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Academic Programs, Office of (George Conneman, Director), 1981-1989 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Academic Programs, Office of (Elizabeth Oltenacu, Associate Director), 1989 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Academic Programs, Office of (Larry Palmer, Vice President), 1988 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Academic Programs, Office of (Larry Palmer, Vice President), 1988 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- ACUSNY (Association of Colleges & Universities of the State of New York), 1989 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Adirondack Fisheries Research, 1980-1989 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Adlerbert, Bo & Lorle (Donors), 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Administrative Services, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Administrative Services, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Admissions, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Admissions, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Admissions & Financial Aid (Susan Murphy, Dean), 1987-1989 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Affirmative Action, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Africa, 1987-1991 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Africa, 1987-1991 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Africa, 1987-1991 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Agricultural & Biological Engineering, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of--Chair, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- Agricultural Engineering, Dept. of, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- Agricultural Engineering, Dept. of, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- Agricultural Engineering, Dept. of, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 31)
- Agricultural Research Initiative, National, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 32)
- Agriculture in the Classroom, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 33)
- Agriculture & Natural Resources, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 34)
- Agronomy, Dept. of, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 35)
- Agronomy, Dept. of, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 36)
- AgSat (Agricultural Satellite Corporation), 1989 (Box 35, Folder 37)
- Agway, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 38)
- Alpha Gamma Rho, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 39)
- Alpha Zeta, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 40)
- Alumni Affairs & Development (John Sterling, Director), 1989 (Box 35, Folder 41)
- Alumni Affairs & Development (John Sterling, Director), 1989 (Box 35, Folder 42)
- Alumni Associations Communications Committee, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 43)
- Alumni Associations Communications Committee, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 44)
- Alumni Associations Communications Committee, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 45)
- American Indian Agiculture Project, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 46)
- American Indian Program, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- American Indian Program, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- American Indian Program, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- American Indian Program, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- American Institute of Cooperation, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Animal Science, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Animal Science, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Animal Science, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Animal Science, Dept. of--Chair, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- (Southeast) Asian Program, 1985-1989 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- (Southeast)Asian Regional Center for Graduate Study & Research in Agriculture--Memo of Agreement, 1976-1989 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Athletic Department, 1985-1989 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- B (General Correspondence), 1983-1989 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Biochemistry, Molecular & Cell Biology, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Biological Sciences, Division of, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Biometrics Unit, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Biotechnology & Agriculture, 1985-1989 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Biotechnology & Agriculture, 1985-1989 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Biotechnology & Agriculture, 1985-1989 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Biotechnology & Agriculture, 1985-1989 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- bST (artificial bovine hormone), 1989 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- C (General Correspondence), 1985-1989 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Campus Affairs (William Gurowitz, Vice President), 1988-1990 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- CARAFE (Coalition for Advancement of Research on Agriculture, Food, and Environment), 1989 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- CARDI (Community and Rural Development Institute), 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Career Development, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- Chemicals/Pesticides Program, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 34)
- Chemicals/Pesticides Program, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Chestnut Research, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 36)
- CIIFAD (Cornell International Institute of Food & Agricultural Development), 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 37)
- CIIFAD (Cornell International Institute of Food & Agricultural Development), 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 38)
- CIIFAD (Cornell International Institute of Food & Agricultural Development), 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 39)
- CIIFAD (Cornell International Institute of Food & Agricultural Development), 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 40)
- CIIFAD (Cornell International Institute of Food & Agricultural Development), 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 41)
- CIIFAD--Proposal, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 42)
- CIIFAD--Proposal, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 43)
- CIIFAD--Proposal, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 44)
- CISER (Cornell Institute for Social and Economic Research), 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 45)
- CISER (Cornell Institute for Social and Economic Research), 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 46)
- Cohn Farm, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Cohn Farm, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Cohn Farm, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Cohn Farm, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Cohn Farm, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Cohn Farm, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Commencement Office, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Communication, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Communication, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Communication, Dept. of--Chair, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Congress, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Controlled Environment Agriculture, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Controlled Environment Agriculture, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Controller, Office of the, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Cooperative Extension, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Cooperative Extension, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Cooperative Extension, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Cooperative Extension, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Cooperative Extension, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Cooperative Extension, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Cooperative Extension, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Cooperative Extension, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Cooperative Extension (Lucinda Noble, Director), 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Cooperative Extension (R. David Smith, Associate Director), 1989 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Cooperative Extension (R. David Smith, Associate Director), 1989 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Cooperative Extension--Representatives, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Cornell Abroad, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Cornell Laboratory for Ecological & Evolutionary Genetics (CLEEG), 1988 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Cornell Plantations, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Cornell Plantations--Personnel, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- Cornell Plantations--Long Range Planning Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Cornell Plantations--Storage Building, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- Corporate Development & Foundation Relations, 1983-1989 (Box 37, Folder 33)
- Counsel, University, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 34)
- County Agents, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 35)
- County Law 224, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- D (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 37)
- Dairy Markets & Policy (Andrew Novakovic, Director), 1986-1989 (Box 37, Folder 38)
- Debt for Equity (Debt to Charitable Institutions), 1988 (Box 37, Folder 39)
- Debt for Equity (Debt to Charitable Institutions), 1988 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- E (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 41)
- Ecology & Systematics, Section of, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 42)
- Education, NYS Dept. of, 1987-1989 (Box 37, Folder 43)
- Education, NYS Dept. of, 1987-1989 (Box 37, Folder 44)
- Education, NYS Dept. of, 1987-1989 (Box 37, Folder 45)
- Education, NYS Dept. of, 1987-1989 (Box 37, Folder 46)
- Education, NYS Dept. of, 1987-1989 (Box 37, Folder 47)
- Education, NYS Dept. of--Teacher Education in Science & Math Program (TESM), 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Empire Farm Days, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Empire State Food & Agricultural Leadership Institute, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Empire State Food & Agricultural Leadership Institute, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Empire State Food & Agricultural Leadership Institute, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Entomology, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Entomology, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Entomology, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Entomology, Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Entrepreneur of the Year Program, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Entrepreneur of the Year Program, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Environmental Sciences, Study Committee on, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Environmental Sciences, Study Committee on, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Equalization & Assessment, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- F (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Facilities--Statutory Office for Capital, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Farming Alternatives Program, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Finance & Business Services, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Finance & Business Services, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Finance & Personnel Office, 1987-1989 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Financial Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Fish & Wildlife Management Board /Cooperative Units (NYS), 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Fish & Wildlife Management Board /Cooperative Units (NYS), 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- Fish & Wildlife Management Board /Cooperative Units (NYS), 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Floriculture & Ornamental Horticulture, Dept. of, 1986-1989 (Box 38, Folder 32)
- Floriculture & Ornamental Horticulture, Dept. of, 1986-1989 (Box 38, Folder 33)
- Floriculture & Ornamental Horticulture, Dept. of--Norm Hummel, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 34)
- Food & Agricultural Sciences, Joint Council on, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 35)
- Food Processing & Development Laboratory, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 36)
- Food Safety Initiative, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 37)
- Food Science, Insitute of / Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 38)
- Food Science, Institute of/ Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 39)
- Food Science, Institute of/ Dept. of, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 40)
- Food Science, Institute of/ Dept. of--Advisory Council, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 41)
- Food Science, Institute of/ Dept. of--Chairmanship, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 42)
- Forensics, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 43)
- 4-H, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 44)
- Frosty Hill Fellowships, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 45)
- G (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 46)
- Gamma Sigma Delta, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 47)
- Genetics & Development, Section of, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 48)
- Genetics & Development, Section of, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 49)
- Genetics & Development, Section of, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 50)
- Gifts--Committee on Acquisition and Use of, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 51)
- Government Affairs, Office of, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Government Affairs, Office of, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Government Affairs, Office of, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Government Affairs, Office of, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Government Affairs, Office of (Robert Barlow, Director of Federal Relations), 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Government Affairs, Office of (Cecelia Roland, Associate Director of Government Affairs-State Relations), 1989 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Government Affairs, Office of (Cecelia Roland, Associate Director of Government Affairs-State Relations), 1989 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Governor, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Grading System / Code of Academic Integrity, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Graduate School, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Graduate School, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Grape & Wine Industry, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- H (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Hansen Property (photos enclosed), 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Hatfield Fellow, 1983-1989 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Human Relations (Joycelyn Hart, Associate Vice President for Human Relations), 1987-1989 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- I (General Correspondence), 1982-1990 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- IAD Steering Committee (International Agriculture), 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- ICET (Institute for Comparative & Environmental Toxicology), 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- ICET (Institute for Comparative & Environmental Toxicology), 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Immunology, Section of, 1988-1990 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Industrial Innovation Extension Service, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Industrial Innovation Extension Service, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Industrial Innovation Extension Service, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Information Technologies (M. Stuart Lynn, Vice President), 1988-1990 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Instruction, Office of, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Instruction, Office of, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Instruction & Teaching Programs, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1988-1990 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1988-1990 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1988-1990 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1988-1990 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- International Agriculture, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- International Agriculture, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- International Agriculture, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- International Memoranda of Agreement, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- International Studies, Center for, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- K (General Correspondence), 1988 (Box 39, Folder 38)
- Kellogg Foundation, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 39)
- Kennedy-Waxman Bill (in re: pesticide residue), 1989 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- L (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- L (General Correspondence), 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 42)
- Landscape Architecture, 1971-1989 (Box 39, Folder 43)
- Landscape Architecture, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 44)
- Landscape Architecture Reaccreditation, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 45)
- Libraries, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 46)
- Life Safety, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 47)
- Long Island Horticultural Research Laboratory, 1985-1988 (Box 39, Folder 48)